const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who was the goalkeeper when David Beckham scored from the halfway line for Manchester United against Wimbledon?",
        choice1: "Shaka Hislop",
        choice2: "Neil Sullivan",
        choice3: "David James",
        choice4: "David Seaman",
        answer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "Which player has made the most Premier League appearances (653)?",
        choice1: "Gareth Barry",
        choice2: "Ryan Giggs",
        choice3: "Frank Lampard",
        choice4: "Gary Speed",
        answer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "Who is the Premier League's all time top scorer (260 goals)?",
        choice1: "Andy Cole",
        choice2: "Sergio Aguero",
        choice3: "Alan Shearer",
        choice4: "Thierry Henry",
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "Which country has won the most World Cups?",
        choice1: "Italy",
        choice2: "Brazil",
        choice3: "Germany",
        choice4: "Argentina",
        answer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",
        choice1: "Manchester United",
        choice2: "Liverpool",
        choice3: "Real Madrid",  
        choice4: "Barcelona",
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "Which team won the European Cup in 1965?",
        choice1: "Manchester United",
        choice2: "Everton",
        choice3: "Lazio",   
        choice4: "West Ham United",
        answer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: "England won the World Cup in 1966, but which club did the goalscorers that day (Martin Peters and Geoff Hurst) play for?",
        choice1: "Leeds",
        choice2: "Arsenal",
        choice3: "Chelsea",  
        choice4: "West Ham United",
        answer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: "Who is the Champions League's top goalscorer of all time?",
        choice1: "Ruud van Nistelrooy",
        choice2: "Robert Lewandowski", 
        choice3: "Christiano Ronaldo",   
        choice4: "Lionel Messi",
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "In which year was the first European Championships held?",
        choice1: "1960",
        choice2: "1956",
        choice3: "1964",    
        choice4: "1968",
        answer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "Denmark beat all the odds and won Euro 92, but they did not even initially qualify, who did they replace to enter the tournament?",
        choice1: "Croatia",
        choice2: "Yugoslavia",
        choice3: "Norway",    
        choice4: "Scotland",
        answer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "Kevin Phillips won the Premier League Golden Boot in 1999/2000, who was the next English player to win it?",
        choice1: "Harry Kane",
        choice2: "Andy Cole",
        choice3: "Michael Owen",   
        choice4: "Alan Shearer",
        answer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "How many times had David Moyes won the prestigious LMA Manager of the year award?",
        choice1: "1",
        choice2: "2",
        choice3: "3",   
        choice4: "4",
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "Ron Atkinson last managed which club in the Premier League?",
        choice1: "Nottingham Forest",
        choice2: "Aston Villa",
        choice3: "Sheffield Wednesday",   
        choice4: "Coventry City",
        answer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "Who scored the first Premier League hat-trick?",
        choice1: "Teddy Sherringham",
        choice2: "Jimmy Floyd Hasselbank",
        choice3: "Gordon Strachan",   
        choice4: "Eric Cantona",
        answer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: "How many times did Sir Alex Ferguson win the Premier League title?",
        choice1: "11",
        choice2: "12",
        choice3: "13",   
        choice4: "14",
        answer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "Due to Covid-19, the 2019/20 Premier League season conculsion was delayed. Who therefore is the only player to score a hat-trick in the Premier League in the month of July?",
        choice1: "Raheem Sterling",
        choice2: "Michael Antonio",
        choice3: "Sadio Mane",   
        choice4: "Mo Salah",
        answer: 2,
    },

]
